=Bossy Husband Who Loved Me= =Episode 8=
= الزوج المتسلط الذي أحبني = = الحلقة 8 =
(My mission is to steal the ledger.)
(مهمتي هي سرقة دفتر الأستاذ.)
(It didn't mention that I can't make a copy of it.)
(لم يذكر أنه لا يمكنني عمل نسخة منه).
(Now I've completed my mission,)
(الآن أكملت مهمتي ،)
(Qin Chuan gets to investigate the corruption case as well.)
(يحصل تشين تشوان أيضًا على التحقيق في قضية الفساد).
(A world where only the dummy Qin Yu)
(عالم لا يوجد فيه سوى دمية تشين يو)
(is hurt.)
(يتألم).
(Mission complete!)
(مهمة مكتملة!)
As for this,
بالنسبة لهذا ،
you can feed the pig.
يمكنك إطعام الخنزير.
This...
هذه...
I...
أنا...
Go.
يذهب.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Oh, Mu Xiaoxi.
أوه ، مو شياوكسي.
You are such a genius!
أنت عبقري!
Damn!
اللعنة!
Who struck the lightning on me again?
من ضربني البرق مرة أخرى؟
Storyline Manager!
مدير القصة!
Storyline Manager, come to the front.
مدير القصة ، تعال إلى المقدمة.
You failed your task.
لقد فشلت مهمتك.
According to the rule of punishment,
وفقا لقاعدة العقوبة ،
not only you will be struck by lightning,
لن يصيبك البرق فقط ،
but also your Back-to-city Piece
ولكن أيضًا قطعة العودة إلى المدينة الخاصة بك
will be deducted by one piece.
بقطعة واحدة.
But I gave the ledger to Qin Yu.
لكنني أعطيت دفتر الأستاذ تشين يو.
Who are you to say I have failed?
من أنت لتقول إنني فشلت؟
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
Because the ledger that you stole was fake
لأن دفتر الأستاذ الذي سرقته كان مزيفًا
So, mission...
لذا ، المهمة ...
Fail!
يفشل!
Fake?
مزيف؟
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
Storyline Manager,
مدير القصة ،
I didn't write this in the novel.
لم أكتب هذا في الرواية.
In the original plot,
في المؤامرة الأصلية ،
Shopkeeper Xu died after being struck by lightning.
توفي صاحب المتجر شو بعد أن ضربه البرق.
But now he isn't dead.
لكنه الآن لم يمت.
The ledger turns out to be a fake one.
تبين أن دفتر الأستاذ مزيف.
What went wrong?
ماذا حصل؟
Are you reading?
هل انت تقرأ؟
Have some tea.
لديك بعض الشاي.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I just passed by
لقد مررت للتو
and saw you.
ورأيتك.
So I come to say hi.
لذلك جئت لألقي التحية.
The second rule is,
القاعدة الثانية هي
do not appear before me unless it's necessary.
لا تحضر أمامي إلا إذا لزم الأمر.
How many times do I have to tell you this?
كم مرة علي أن أخبرك بهذا؟
Oh, come on. We've known each other
اووه تعال.  لقد عرفنا بعضنا البعض
for quite some time.
لبعض الوقت.
Why do you go off all of a sudden?
لماذا تنفجر فجأة؟
What if I wanted to?
ماذا لو أردت؟
I just wanted to remind you.
أردت فقط أن أذكرك.
Have you ever thought
هل فكرت يوما
that Shopkeeper Xu brought you a piece of fake evidence?
أن صاحب المتجر (شو) أحضر لك قطعة من الأدلة المزيفة؟
Ridiculous!
سخيف!
Do you think I'm as ignorant as you?
هل تعتقد أنني جاهل مثلك؟
Furthermore,
بالإضافة إلى،
you're my wife in name only.
أنت زوجتي بالاسم فقط.
Stop meddling
توقف عن التدخل
in my business.
في عملي.
Why are you being so aggressive today?
لماذا أنت عدواني جدا اليوم؟
How can I be polite
كيف أكون مؤدبًا
to someone like you?
لشخص مثلك
(Damn it, Qin Chuan.)
(اللعنة ، تشين تشوان.)
I even went against the original plot
حتى أنني ذهبت ضد الحبكة الأصلية
and copied a ledger
ونسخ دفتر الأستاذ
for you to investigate the case.
لكي تحقق في القضية.
(No good deed goes unpunished!)
(لا يمر عمل جيد بلا عقاب!)
Fine.
بخير.
You wanted to create boundaries, right?
أردت إنشاء حدود ، أليس كذلك؟
I get it.
أحصل عليه.
Wait a minute.
انتظر دقيقة.
Wait?
انتظر؟
If I appear before you again,
إذا حضرت أمامك مرة أخرى ،
I'll write my name backward.
سأكتب اسمي بالمقلوب.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
the ledger is indeed
هو في الواقع دفتر الأستاذ
identical to the fake ledger
مطابق لدفتر الأستاذ المزيف
that I copied.
الذي نسخته.
Same content. Will not affect the investigation.
نفس المحتوى.  لن يؤثر على التحقيق.
She stole the ledger
لقد سرقت دفتر الأستاذ
to help Prince Tan, that was obvious.
لمساعدة الأمير تان ، كان ذلك واضحًا.
But, leaving an identical copy
لكن ، ترك نسخة متطابقة
would make all the efforts go in vain.
سيجعل كل الجهود تذهب سدى.
In this way,
في هذا الطريق،
Prince Tan will think that you lost the ledger
سوف يعتقد الأمير تان أنك فقدت دفتر الأستاذ
and he might let his guard down,
وقد يتخلى عن حذره ،
making the process of investigation easier.
جعل عملية التحقيق أسهل.
With that being said,
بالإضافة إلى ما قيل،
Her Highness wasn't helping Prince Tan,
صاحبة السمو لم تكن تساعد الأمير تان ،
she was helping you.
كانت تساعدك.
But,
ولكن،
why would she help me?
لماذا ستساعدني
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
everyone in the capital knows
يعلم الجميع في العاصمة
Her Highness's love for you.
حب سموها لك.
When she knew
عندما علمت
Prince Tan was targeting you,
كان الأمير تان يستهدفك ،
she came forward.
تقدمت.
She does one thing under cover of another.
إنها تفعل شيئًا تحت غطاء آخر.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
Don't you think so?
ألا تعتقد ذلك؟
Well, she did use me.
حسنًا ، لقد استخدمتني.
But she did help me
لكنها ساعدتني
in this matter.
فى هذا الشأن.
I was wrong about her.
كنت مخطئا عنها.
Right,
الصحيح،
the mysterious Yuan Giant
العملاق الغامض اليوان
seemed to be involved too.
يبدو أنه متورط أيضًا.
Hurry up with the investigation.
اسرع في التحقيق.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
since you can listen to Her Highness's inner voice,
حيث يمكنك الاستماع إلى صوت سموها الداخلي ،
why don't you start from her?
لماذا لا تبدأ منها
Listen to it more often,
استمع إليها كثيرًا ،
there must be something.
يجب أن يكون هناك شيء.
Great minds think alike.
العقول العظيمة تفكر على حد سواء.
Your Highness!
صاحب السمو!
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Her Highness just packed and leave.
حزمتها سموها للتو وغادر.
She went back to her maiden home.
عادت إلى منزلها قبل الزواج.
Xixi,
يتبول،
you've only been gone for two days.
لقد ذهبت لمدة يومين فقط.
Why did you come back?
لماذا عدت؟
We broke up.
لقد انفصلنا.
As of today,
اعتبارًا من اليوم ،
Qin Chuan and I
أنا تشين تشوان
are officially separated.
يتم فصلها رسميا.
Nonsense!
كلام فارغ!
Couples might inevitably
الأزواج قد لا محالة
fight sometimes.
قتال في بعض الأحيان.
Your mother and I fought too.
قاتلنا أنا وأمك أيضًا.
Your mother's temper was terribly...
كان مزاج والدتك رهيبًا ...
reasonable.
مسؤول.
Xixi.
يتبول.
Regarding this,
بخصوص هذا ،
you shall learn from me.
يجب أن تتعلم مني.
It's common for couples
إنه شائع للأزواج
to have disagreements.
أن يكون هناك خلافات.
Do not take it seriously.
لا تأخذ الأمر على محمل الجد.
Whatever. I'm not going back.
ايا كان.  لن أعود.
Sir.
سيد.
Prince Rui is at the door.
الأمير روي عند الباب.
What is he doing here?
ماذا يفعل هنا؟
Don't let him in.
لا تسمح له بالدخول.
Let him in!
دعه يدخل!
He's my son-in-law. There's no need to be so polite.
إنه زوج ابنتي.  ليس هناك حاجة لأن تكون مؤدبًا جدًا.
Let him in.
دعه يدخل.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Xixi.
يتبول.
Help His Highness with the food.
ساعد سموه بالطعام.
No.
رقم.
It's okay.
حسنا.
I can help myself.
يمكنني مساعدة نفسي.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
my daughter
ابنتي
was spoiled by her mother.
أفسدتها والدتها.
She must bring you a lot of trouble.
يجب أن تجلب لك الكثير من المتاعب.
I...
أنا...
I didn't treat her well too.
أنا لم أعاملها جيدًا أيضًا.
Your Highness, you're exaggerating.
صاحب السمو ، أنت تبالغ.
It's common for a couple
إنه شائع للزوجين
to have disagreements.
أن يكون هناك خلافات.
Right.
الصحيح.
You are officially married and had your first night together.
أنت متزوج رسميًا وقد أمضيت الليلة الأولى معًا.
You can overcome everything.
يمكنك التغلب على كل شيء.
It's good to talk it out.
من الجيد التحدث عنها.
First night...
الليلة الأولى...
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟